Hey, how you doing, Josh?
>> Good. How are you?
>> I'm doing great. You? I like your
background.
>> Well, thank you. It's a be beautiful
day. Um,
>> why Atlanta? What was what makes uh
Atlanta the right fit for you?
>> I mean, everything about Atlanta, the
the things they're accomplishing last
year and the things they're going to
accomplish in these upcoming years, the
defense, it fits me, it fits what I do.
So, that's exactly why I want to be here
and the people that's here.
I wonder what you thought your NFL
career was going to be coming out of
Wagner. I mean, you're enter you're
about to enter year five. Is that what
you thought saw in your mind? Is that a
surprise to you? What where are you on
your path?
>> Um, my thing is just being present and
taking every day as it is. And you hear
about the trials and tribulations coming
from a program like that, being
undrafted, but like as long as you just
be present and just make sure you could
take advantage of every little
opportunity, you never know where you're
going to end up. So, would I say I'm
surprised? No. I always had high
expectations of myself, even if people
didn't and I continue to do. But, um,
I'm just excited to keep seeing where
this is going to take me, though.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you, Josh. Anyone
else?
>> I'll keep going if if if nobody else has
got one. I just didn't want to hog the
hog the mic.
>> Go ahead.
>> Uh Ian Cunningham said earlier today
that you sort of fit the way Jeff
Albrich likes to play. Um how do how
would you describe the way you like to
play and how it fits in what Atlanta
does?
>> Exactly. Being on the edge of guys
attacking, working for as one on the
Dline. uh penetrating backfield
presence, disrupting even if it ain't
making the play. That's all they want
from three texts, getting off the ball.
And if you watch film and watch the
years I've been productive and been in
defenses like this, and every year I
evolve into a better player. So, I can't
wait to see what I do this year.
>> How how much, if any, did your
relationship with Ian um give you a
comfort level about coming to Atlanta
just having spent two years together in
Chicago?
>> A lot. cuz it's a guy that's seen me
while I was in Chicago, seen the things
I can do and um so I know he he'll he
he'll know how to utilize me and put me
in the right positions and just to hear
that he want me here makes me excited to
come here and play hard for him.
>> Thank you. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, too.
>> Anyone else?
>> I swear I don't bite.
>> All right. Thanks, guys.
>> Appreciate y'all. You have a great day.
Hi, Channing. Josh Kendall from The
Athletic. Nice to see you.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> What um what about Atlanta made this a
good fit for you? I imagine sort of a
homecoming was part of it, but what
else?
>> Um I've been bleeding black and red for
a long time now. Just going to
University of Georgia. Most of my
family's here. My aunts and uncles
literally live in Lawrenceville,
Georgia. So, I'm very in tune to the
culture here and just love to be back.
How do you think you fit this defense
specifically?
>> Um, uh, this a new coaching staff, but
from what I've seen, it's a lot more uh,
they want to run a 4-3 and then switch
from a 4-3 to a 34. So, that requires a
lot of versatility, and I feel like my
game speaks for itself in terms of
versatility. So, I feel like I fit that
mold perfect.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
Go ahead, Justin.
Hey Channing. Uh, welcome back of course
to the state of Georgia. They're also,
you know, Aziz coming in as well. How do
you feel like your your time at UG,
Coach Smart, prepared you for the NFL
level? man, they've distilled so many
factors into me in terms of just getting
to know my teammate, things off the
field, just getting to know my
teammates, uh, practicing the
fundamentals and just the mentality and
mindset that you have to have on an
everyday basis, not getting too high or
too low and staying on that medium to
get where you are now. So, I keep that
with me and I keep those qualities and
traits that he taught me to this day.
>> And obviously, you know, you got the UG
connections and stuff. Are there any
players on this defense already that
you're coming in that you've got a
relationship with, whether it's from
training or whatever, that you're able
to like pick their brain before signing
or you're looking forward to to lining
up alongside?
>> Uh, of course, Jaylen Walker is here and
then Charlie Warner as well, even though
he's on the offensive side of the ball,
but like I've been chopping it up with
uh Jaylen specifically because we're
both from the Carolina. He's from North,
but I'm from the south, but we're still
from the same kind of area. So,
specifically him really. Yeah.
>> All right. Go ahead, Ken.
>> Hey, Jenny. Um, what did they what did
they tell you about kind of what they
saw in you? How they how they envisioned
your your role?
>> Uh, I haven't talked to them about my
role or how they envisioned me, but just
from what I see from a schematic
standpoint, I know coach O is here as
well, uh, special teams coach. So just
from a versatility standpoint, it could
it could be anything. So we uh that's to
be continued. I really don't know yet.
>> Yeah. And then special teams
coordinator, you have you have a pass
with him. You
>> Yeah, he was at uh he was with Miami
Dolphins for a little bit.
>> Okay.
>> What did you do there special teams?
>> Uh I was a four phase guy there. So
Okay.
>> All right. Anybody else? Josh, do you
have another one?
>> Yeah, I'll go I'll go again with one
more. Channing Ian Cunningham said
earlier today that he saw this whole
group uh as or several people among this
whole group of free agents as guys who
not only had a chance to help the
Falcons, but would would have a chance
to prove themselves maybe a step further
than they had already in their career. I
wonder if you see this opportunity the
same for yourself. I look at every year
as a year to get better. So regardless,
especially here with the with Ian
Cunningham saying that like I'm going to
take the most of my uh take the most out
the opportunity that's been presented
upon me and I'm just going to work from
there. I don't really want to say too
much. I just want to get to work and
show through my actions at this point.
>> Thank you for your time. Good to see
you.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Anybody else have anything?
>> All right. Thanks, y'all.
>> Hey, uh Jake, how are you? Good. How are
you doing, Ken?
>> Good. Appreciate your time. Um,
well, first, uh, I guess kind of
obviously kind of just describe your
process of of deciding uh on the
Falcons.
Yeah, it was uh it was an interesting
process because you know I I was coming
from Miami and
Coach Aerman was was there last year and
you know it I loved how we operated last
year so I kind of just wanted to keep it
rolling and why not even do it in a dome
too. So it was an easy choice.
Um, tell me what is I mean he's it's
interesting. There have been a number of
of signes that that he's had uh with him
either in Miami or elsewhere. What is it
about the way he does things that made
it attractive to you to continue working
with him?
>> Yeah, I I I really like how he sets up
punt team specifically and then all the
other like kickoff kickoff return. He
he's he lets the punter or like the
kickoff returner guy, he he puts
everybody in a really good place where
they can execute and just play super
fast and and not really think about
their their job while they're doing it.
Um so, you know, I I trust him a ton. I
trust all the guys he puts in front of
me a ton and I'm really excited to see
how this year goes.
>> Yeah. Um, in terms of the way he does
that with you, can you speak a little
more to that? Just the way he helps you
and kind of, you know, helps you do your
job well.
>> Yeah. Um,
specifically last year, I I feel like I
got better a lot. I I mean, he brought
in competition for me last year in
training camp. Um, and that was a huge
moment in my football career and life,
just kind of having to put your nose
down and and figure it out. And he
challenges me a ton and I I appreciate
that in hindsight. Um, so he he's he's
not afraid to challenge his players and
I think he really does get the best out
of everybody.
>> Yeah. And as far as being in a dome, can
you I imagine that must be a welcoming
uh facet of of playing for the Falcons.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it is. It is a positive.
Definitely not a negative.
>> In 2020, you were you you earned all Pro
and Pro Bowl and I suppose one of those
things like if you know if you could
figure out exactly what it was that
happened, but can you kind of speak
going back to that season, what what
were some of the factors then that
enabled you to to play at such a high
level?
Yeah, a little bit of everything. I
mean, at the punting position, the the
most important word is consistency, and
you just want to be consistent. Um, I
loved how I was punting the ball that
year. I loved how I was punting the ball
many other years, too. Um, and there's
just there's so many other factors that
can come down to if you make the the one
out of 32 list. you know, there's
there's 31 other extremely good punters
out there that are also having really
good years, too. So, it's it's a little
bit of luck, but
>> yeah.
>> Yeah, it's funny. I mean, I would think
maybe it was, you know, your your
punting average, but I think sometime
that's a matter of field position and
you're not like kicking the ball 48
yards isn't always the right thing. I'm
curious like do you feel like that year
you actually played significantly better
than the other years or or it was just
more like you're saying kind of a a lot
of things rolling into it?
>> Yeah. With punting stats are so
interesting because you know last year
for example on the Falcons Bradley had a
ton of short punts. Uh short as in there
wasn't a ton of field position to to
play with. Um, and you know that that's
a huge play for a punter to make your
team uh do well and succeed because you
can punt pin the guy inside the 10. Um,
but you know, you're not going to hit a
70 yard punt on that one. So, it's
punting stats are always a little weird
because you there's so many variables
that aren't factored in when you're just
looking at gross or you're just looking
at net. Um, you know, like for example,
my net last year on Miami, we we were
solid all the way up until we played the
Jets the second time and then the guy
returned a punt on us and for for a
touchdown and then, you know, your net
average for the entire season drops a
yard and a half just on one play.
>> So, there there's so many variables, so
many factors, and you know, everybody
else, there's 31 other guys that are
playing through those variables and
factors, too. Um, so it's a little bit
of luck.
>> Yeah.
And one last thing, do you have any
connection with Atlanta?
>> Oh, um, I really don't. I, you know, one
of my closestish friends from college is
from Atlanta and that's about it. You
know, my snapper from Miami, my first
two years is from Atlanta. Um, I know
Liam the snapper here
and you know, not not a ton of
connections, but I'm excited. I I was
out there yesterday and we we loved it.
>> Very good,
>> Josh.
>> You're muted.
>> Muted is here.
I I apologize, Jake. I should know all
of this by now.
>> 15 yard penalty.
>> I know. Um, forgive me. And a second
time because I jumped on a minute late.
So, if I if you've been asked about your
relationship with Craig, uh, y'all y'all
crossed paths, right?
>> We did. Yeah. Last year in Miami, and it
was it was great.
>> Yeah, it they they did ask that the
first question, but I can reiterate it.
It was just it was awesome to you know
it was a new special teams coach for me
in Miami last year and he actually
brought in his his guy his competition
for me. Um, and it was a true, you know,
best man win kind of a thing. And it
challenged me a ton. And I appreciate
that a lot in hindsight because I I feel
like I got better as a punter from the
year 2025.
>> And I imagine that sort of increased
your from your comfort level coming to a
new place, you know, a guy, you know,
>> without a doubt. Yeah.
>> And obviously you spent some time with
Tua. What what are you know give us your
scouting report on on Tua as a
quarterback.
>> Scouting report on Tua. Um he's a great
guy. I think we had the number one
offense in 2023.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, I'm not I'm not sure there's
many quarterbacks out there that that
had the number one offense, which is I I
think he's an impressive football player
and I'm excited to see what his future
holds.
>> Thank you. Nice to meet you. Nice to
meet you too, Josh.
>> Any more questions?
>> Hey, uh Jan, uh thank you for your time.
Uh I guess first to start just, uh can
you share how you uh came your decision
to sign with Falcons?
>> Yeah. Um yeah, first of all, nice to
meet you. Um but yeah,
>> it was uh it was a fairly easy decision
for me. um after the negotiations and
the constant talks with my agent and you
know seeing what the interests were from
teams around the league um the Falcons
were at the the very top of you know
that that line or that food chain um and
you know for me it was it's about
alignment um going into year five in my
career and you know you know I need an
offense and a offensive coordinator and
a head coach who aligns with you know
what I believe in what I can bring to a
team and you know I felt like the
Falcons were the right place for me.
>> When you say alignment uh what were some
of the things you were looking for?
>> Yeah. Um a young coach um a young OC uh
like coach Tommy Reese. Um you know a
team that you know is in need for wide
receiver help and you know a team that I
know that can use you know my value as a
wide receiver. Um, and those are all
things that, you know, going throughout
this process, talking back and forth
with my agent, those are all things that
was expressed to me, um, that that are
in need for the Falcons and, you know, I
can be that perfect asset.
>> Yeah.
>> How would you describe your the kind of
the arc of your career to this point?
>> Yeah. Um, it's kind of been a roller
coaster. um you know, starting out being
a a first round draft pick. Um and
coming into Washington and you know,
having to to be a number two wide
receiver for the first time in my
career. Um and you know, having success
at that um and you know, being able to
show my my capability of what I can do
on the football field and then you know,
a quick turnaround of being traded uh
right before year three starts um to a a
team with, you know, a bunch of
superstars, as you guys know. Um, you
know, there's only there's only one ball
that can go around. Um, and that was
pretty tough for me to to understand at
first, but you know, I got the grasp of
it real quick.
>> Um, and you know, I was I was just able
to fit in, you know, where I where I got
to fit in. Um, and you know, my role
kind of got minimized a little bit. So,
um, that that was that was a big thing
for me uh, in year three and four. Um,
and now going into year five, you know,
like I said, um, the the big thing that
for me was going to a team where I feel
like my talent will be on display. Um,
and my talent can be showcased. Um, I
I've learned a lot in my first four
years in the NFL from some great wide
receivers, um, great coaches. Um, but I
feel like now is really my time to to
put my talents on on display.
Um we uh Ian Cunningham book this
morning and and he was you know he he
was speaking on the the the fact that
they've signed uh a lot of you know kind
of guys that look like depth guys maybe
guys that have started some but not a
lot and it sounded like to me you know
they were honing in on guys maybe that
are a little overlooked uh maybe just
need an opportunity. I'm curious. You
you from the way you talk, it sounds
like you kind of see yourself that way.
>> 100%. Um I'm definitely one of those
guys who, you know, I I 100% believe in
my talent, my ability to to make plays
in this football league. Um it's just
about getting the opportunity to to do
so. Um and I I didn't really have the
opportunity the past couple years. Um
but now I'm looking into year five and
year one with the Falcons to to really
do that. Um, and I can't wait to make
plays for this football team.
>> Great. Thank you,
>> Mara.
>> Hey, Jan. Welcome to Atlanta. Um, can
you just talk about your familiarity
with this offense, whether there's any
players that maybe you've trained with,
worked closely with in the past, and
what you think you specifically can
bring to the offense this year?
>> How you doing? Um, I appreciate
appreciate the the welcome to Atlanta.
Um, you know, I've I've done a little
bit of research. uh myself on coach
Stfani. Um a great mind uh a great
offensive mind. Um that that was big for
me. Um coach Tommy Reese, another young
developing
big newcomer in this in this league. Um
and that that was another thing that was
big for me. And you know, I got to reach
out to some people. I talked to Kenny
Picket who was with the Browns with
Coach Stfansky. Um and you know, he he
had nothing but great things to say
about him. Um, I talked to my old
receivers's coach and my old head coach,
Coach Serriani, and, you know, they
speak very fondly of coach Stfansky. Um,
and those are those are some things
that, you know, I've already knew coming
into this. So, you know, I'm I was
really happy with my decision. Um, I was
really happy with, you know, the way the
way things went about. Um, and I'm I'm
excited to be a Falcon.
>> Josh.
Hey, Jan. Josh Kendall with The
Athletic. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you as well.
>> Do you see yourself as a slot guy, as an
outside guy? Do you Is there one spot
where you're more comfortable or do you
feel like you're going to sort of bounce
back and forth in Atlanta?
>> Yeah. Um, for me, what plays to my skill
set is being able to play everywhere on
the football field. Um, being able to
play inside, play outside, um, show my
position versatility. Um there there's
not a place that I feel more comfortable
than the other. Um
is something that I've been doing ever
since my freshman year in college. You
know, I' I've been able to move inside
and outside and, you know, make plays
wherever. Um and and that's something
that I'm really looking forward to in in
this offense.
It sounded like from something you said
earlier, I just but I just wanted to
clarify that part of the draw for
Atlanta for you was the opportunity to
be on the field and and to show, you
know, to to get snaps.
How motivated do you feel to prove
yourself?
>> Extremely um more than more than I could
sit here on on this Zoom and tell you
about. Um,
just for me, you know, being that, you
know, I was a a firstround talent, um, a
guy who had a lot of success in college,
a guy who had a lot of success in in my
first couple years in Washington, um,
with not that many opportunities, um,
and then kind of taking a back seat in
my third and fourth year. You know, I'm
I I feel like I've been I've been
holding all this in for the past couple
years. Um, I feel like, you know, I'm
ready to to just show the world what I
can do. Um, and Coach Deansky, he he's
given me the opportunity and, you know,
I can't wait. I can't wait to just take
it.
>> Great. Thank you. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you as well.
>> Anybody else have any other questions?
>> All set.
>> Josh, you all good?
>> I'm all good. Thank you, Taylor. Thank
you, Johan.
>> Thank you, John.
>> All right, you guys.
>> Thanks, John. Thanks, John.
>> Thank you.
>> Josh Kendall with the athletic. Nice to
meet you.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Kind of I guess why Atlanta is the first
question. What was what was the drawing
interest here?
>> Um it's uh it's my hometown. I was I
grew up in Dula, Georgia, probably 20
minutes from the facility. Um and then a
familiar face with uh Bill Callahan as
the O line coach.
Um, I I enjoyed my last couple years
with him.
>> Give us your scouting report of Bill
Callahan. What should folks expect from
the offensive line?
>> Uh, you know, we're going to work really
hard. We're going to work hard together.
Um, he expects he expects a lot out of
us. Um, and he's really going to make us
come together as a group. Um, that's one
thing that I realized in Tennessee. We
we became a pretty tight-knit group.
um obviously through the things that
happened there in Tennessee. Um but he
had a big part to do with that and uh
you know he's he's very technical. Um
he's got a way to move and train
everything. Um so it it's exciting. He
definitely in year eight of my career he
uh helped me tap into a little bit more
of myself.
>> You're in mute Josh.
So, what are your expectations for your
role here? Did they communicate with you
sort of where you stand or is it pretty
open-ended from your
>> Um, well, you know, the offensive line
here is is a great group. Um, they have
respect around the league and they work
well together. So, uh, as far as my
expectations, I I expect to come in and
just contribute where I can, um,
wherever that may be. Last year, I
played four or five different positions,
including a a jumbo and a fullback spot.
So, um, really just taking advantage of
opportunities when they come, being
ready to go if my numbers called upon.
and cohesion is like you mentioned so
big up there up front, you know, how
incumbent is it on you as a new guy to
sort of catch up with what that back
group is doing and fit in there?
>> Um, well, anytime you come somewhere
new, um, and you know, I'm not a rookie.
I'm I'm year nine, year 10, you know, I'
I've seen how different rooms can work.
Um, so really you just you you want to
go in there, make sure you know
everybody knows that they can trust you,
that they can count on you, you can be
dependable. Uh, you don't want to step
on any toes or anything like that. Um,
from the start, you try to harbor good
relationships and then hopefully, you
know, you just kind of they bring you
in, you know what I mean? You become
part of the group.
>> Thank you.
>> Yep.